You lost your father's car. Sold your prom date. And
a guy named 'Tito' wants you dead.
The Night Before is a comedy, romance film directed by Thom Eberhardt.
A popular beauty surprisingly asks a nerd to take her to the prom.
He wakes up hours later in a sleazy alley.
She's missing but he remembers nothing about it.
Winston Connelly, played by Keanu Reeves.
Tara Mitchell, played by Lori Loughlin.
Rhonda, played by Theresa Saldana.
Tito, played by Trinidad Silva.
Lisa, played by Suzanne Snyder.
Tuff #2, played by Ned Bellamy.
The Night Before is a 1988 American comedy film
starring Keanu Reeves and Lori Loughlin.
Reeves plays Winston Connelly, the so-called high school
nerd and vice president of the astronomy club.
Loughlin plays Tara Mitchell, the pretty and popular head cheerleader
who also happens to be the local police chief's daughter.
The Tagline was: "You lost your father's car, sold your prom
date and a guy called 'Tito' wants you dead.
It's a date that's the time of your life."
The film explores themes of amnesia, handcuffs, tied up.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.